Sell ​​by the meter, sell the idea, how it
works.
We try to sell the ideas,
okay,
but then we have to finalize the
meters.  As you've seen, the factory
produces meters. We are a
manufacturer, but if
we weigh and measure our product in terms of
composition, it certainly has costs,
higher prices than a
Turkish manufacturer, an Asian manufacturer,
and this is precisely where I was telling you, we
sell ideas because the way
we use these raw materials doesn't equal
the price per meter, which is higher
than that of a manufacturer or a
fast factory. This is justified by the
quality.  I see that the balance sheets in
recent years have been very good and therefore the
answer is certainly justified.